Philip M. Wagner papers
1839-1995
bulk 1942-1989
Coll001
Wagner, Philip M. (Philip Marshall); 1904-
8 boxes (9.35 linear feet)
Files documenting Philip Wagner's career as a freelance columnist, writer and editor for the Baltimore Sun and Baltimore Evening Sun, and founder of Boordy Vineyard. Includes correspondence, manuscripts, clippings, research files, case files, publications, diaries, notes and photos. Significant correspondents represented are: Alfred Knopf, H.L. Mencken, Knowles Ryerson, Knud Meister, Ann Duchene, Lord Winster.
University of Maryland, Baltimore County Albin O. Kuhn Library and Gallery UMBC 1000 Hilltop Circle Baltimore, MD 21250 410-455-2353 speccoll@umbc.edu
This collection of Philip Wagner’s papers covers the three main areas of his professional life: his work as a free lance columnist, as an editor and writer for the Baltimore Sun, and as a vintner and founder of Boordy Vineyard. The bulk of the papers however pertains to his work as a writer both for the Baltimore Sun and for his syndicated column from the early 1950’s to the late 1970’s.
The collection contains a substantial amount of correspondence, manuscripts, clippings and research files, along with some notes, receipts and invoices, and publications, the majority of which directly relate to the articles he produced and illustrate the scope of his intrests. Among those he corresponded with were editors and writers for the Manchester Guardian and the London Times, Alfred Knopf his publisher, the American Society of Newspaper Editors of which he was a member, and Lord Winster a free lance columnist in London who contributed articles to the Sun for many years. That he had a wide range of contacts both in the U.S. and Europe is particularly apparent in the correspondence connected with his several European trips. These trips were a for him a combination of work and pleasure serving both as a chance to meet with his contacts and those who were sources for his articles as well as an opportunity to visit th vinyards and wineries in France.
A significant portion of the manuscripts in the collection are from his syndicated column on public affairs which he wrote from 1963 until nearly the end of his life. Also included are drafts of his work on H.L. Mencken and a selection of editorials written for the Sun, both in manuscript draft and proof sheets. Of particular intrest are those editorial proofs marked “killed editorial" as these were never published. Wagner also kept a small number of manuscripts by other writers among which were articles submitted by Lord Winsterfor publication in the Sun between 1952-1961.
Philip Wagner’s collection of clippings and research files contains a large number of subject files collected both for research on his syndicated column and his work at the Sun. The topics cover a wide range of subjects but show that he had a keen interest in foreign affairs and in government. Topics included the European Common Market in 1965, the Bay of Pigs, congressional reform, fiscal policies and budget and also in individual politicians and policies. He had a particular intrest in the Freedom of Information Act and in the issue of Forest Genetics maintaining a substantial file on each. Further he had a penchant for issues that were controversial such as Madelyn Murray and the school prayer issue, the Jensen I.Q. study, the Motorola discrimination suit of 1964 and the impact of automation. His clipping files also contained copies of his syndicated column for the years February 1964 - January 1971, articles published by the Sun of particular interest to him, and a large quantity of miscellaneous clippings from a wide range of sources on a vast array of subjects.
Though more limited in scope the collection also contains documents pertaining to his work as an editor and to his personal avocation, winemaking. There are memoranda, case files, notes, correspondence, receipts and invoices, diaries, photos, and scrapbooks.
Organized into three series: Series I. Personal, 1839-1994. Series II. Sun Papers, 1927-1995. Series III. Boordy Vineyard, 1933-1995.
Series I. Personal
Correspondence
Manuscripts
Clippings
Research Files
Publications
Journals and Pamphlets
Receipts and Invoices
Diaries
Photos
Flyers, Announcements, & Miscellany
Notes and Notebooks
Series II. Sun Papers
Correspondence
Manuscripts
Proof Sheets
Clippings
Research Files
Case Files
Notes
Reports
Memoranda
Press Releases
Publications
Photos
Series III. Boordy Vineyards
Correspondence
Press Releases
Clippings
Pamphlets
Diary
Miscellany
Photos
No restrictions.
Philip Wagner papers, #6928. Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Knopf Alfred A. 1892-1984; Mencken H. L. (Henry Louis) 1880-1956; Ryerson Knowles Augustus 1892-1990; Meister Knud; Duchene Ann; Winster Lord; Boordy Vineyard; Wagner, Philip M. (Philip Marshall), 1904- Archives; Editorials Maryland Baltimore; Viticulture Maryland
- Series I. Personal, 1839-1994; bulk 1950-1983; 6 boxes (7.5 linear feet)
  Correspondence, manuscripts, clippings, research files and other materials relating to Wagners work as a free lance writer as well as personal correspondence, diaries, notebooks, photos and miscellany are arranged into 11 subseries by type of document.
  - Sub-series I.A. Correspondence, 1915-1994; bulk 1930-1980; 31 folders (.5 linear feet )
    Correspondence files for individuals, associations, newspapers, and trips abroad are arranged in alphabetical order, followed by Miscellaneous correspondence in chronological order.
    - ASNE (American Society of Newspaper Editors) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Echenstein, Christopher (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - European trips 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - European trips 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - European trips 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - European trips 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - European trips 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Harazthy, Arpad; 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Knopft, Alfred; 1951-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Manchester Guardian 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - McGurk, Frank 1953-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Meister, Knud 1949-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Mencken, H.L. 1936-1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Newstatesman & Nation 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Rowland Park School 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Ryerson, Knowles 1948-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Theime, E. Thurston 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Violins 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1931-1939 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1941-1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sub-series I.B. Manuscripts- Syndicated Columns & Miscellaneous, 1925-1984; bulk 1950-1978; 112 folders (2.25 linear feet)
    Manuscripts for syndicated columns are arranged in chronological order followed by miscellaneous manuscripts: titled manuscripts in alphabetical order first, followed by untitled ones in chronological order, then untitled and undated manuscripts and manuscripts not by Philip Wagner.
    - Syndicated Columns - 1963 (Sept-Oct) (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1963 (Nov-Dec) (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Jan-Feb) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (March-April) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (May-June) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (July- Aug) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Sept-Oct) (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Nov-Dec) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Jan-Feb) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (March-April) (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (May-June) (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (July-Aug) (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Sept-Oct) (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Nov-Dec) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Jan-Feb) (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (March-April) (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (May-June) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (July-Aug) (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Spet-Oct) (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Spet-Oct) (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Jan-Feb) (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (March-April) (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (May-June) (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Marcc-April) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1972 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1972 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1972 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1972 (July-August) (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1972 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1972 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1973 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1973 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1973 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1973 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1973 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1973 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1974 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1974 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1974 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1974 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1974 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1974 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1975 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1975 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1975 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1975 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1975 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1975 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1976 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1976 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1976 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1976 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1976 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1976 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1977 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1977 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1977 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1977 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1977 (Sept-Oct) (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1977 (Nov-Dec) (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1978 (Jan-Feb) (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1978 (March-April) (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1978 (May-June) (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1978 (July-Aug) (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1978 (Sept) (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous - Back Door Tactics in Big Business (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous - Claims to Distinction (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Contribution to American Culture (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Crop Limitations: Farewell and Hail (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous - Government and Heresy (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous - Home Life of 20th Century Americans (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous - In Honor of Their Alma Mater (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous - Let Farmer Provide His Own Farm Relief (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous - Mencken, H.L. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous - On Having a Brilliant Day (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous - Portrait of an Intellectual Marytr (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous - Wine & Aestetics (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1925, 1937, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled - Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Manuscripts not by Wagner (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series III.C. Clippings, 147 folders (1.25 linear feet)
    Subject files arranged in alphabetical order may contain a variety of clippings, correspondence, pamphlets, photographs, and notes.
    - Subject Files - Acheson, Dean (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Abdication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Agnew, Spiro T (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Apalachia (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Apportionment (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Argintina & Brazil 1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Automation 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Baltimore Power Brokers 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Bay of Pigs (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Biological Warfare 1964 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bolivia 1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bracero Law 1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Canada - Quebec 1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Chinatown/Ruth Newell (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - CIA, Singapore Episode (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Congo & Nigeria 1964 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Congress, Reform of 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Conservatism, In defense of (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Crime & Law Enforcement - LBJ message 1965 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Criminal Law - Defense of the guilty 1964-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - DDT 1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Eastern Bloc 1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - European Common Market 1965 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Famine & Food as Diplomacy 1965 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Filibuster 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Fiscal Policies - Budget, Federalism and the Great Society (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Indonesia & Malaysia 1964 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - I.Q. Jensen Study 1969 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Jenkins, Walter - Scandel 1964 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Kennedy, Robert and Edward (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Labor 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Latin America - OAS/Common Market 1965 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Latin America - Trade Block 1964 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Libel - Cup Street case 19964 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Medicare 1964 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Mexico 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Miscegenation - Florida Case 1964 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Motorola - Discrimination Suit 1964 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Murray, Madalyn - School Prayer Issue 1964 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Nassar (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Nato Multilateral Force 1964 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - News American Folds (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Niagra Falls 1945-1951 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Vietnam/South East Asia - Guerrilla Warfare/ Mekong River Project 1965 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Miscellaneous - 1839, 1855 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous - 1913 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous - 1923 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous - 1936 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous - 1937 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Miscellaneous - 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous - 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Miscellaneous - 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous - 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Miscellaneous - 1960 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Miscellaneous - 1961 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Miscellaneous - 1962 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Miscellaneous - 1963 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Miscellaneous - 1964 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous - 1965 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Miscellaneous - 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Miscellaneous - 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Miscellaneous - 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous - 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Miscellaneous - 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous - 1990’s (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous - undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Mar) (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (April) (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (May) (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (June) (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (July) (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1964 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Mar) (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (April) (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (May) (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (June) (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (July) (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1965 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Mar) (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (April) (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (May) (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (June) (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (July) (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1966 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Mar) (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (April) (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (May) (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (June) (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (July) (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1967 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Mar) (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (April) (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (May) (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (June) (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (July) (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1968 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Mar) (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (April) (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (May) (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (June) (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (July) (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1969 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Feb) (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (May) (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (June) (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (July) (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Aug) (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Sept) (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Oct) (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Nov) (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1970 (Dec) (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Syndicated Columns - 1971 (Jan) (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Sub-series I.D. Research Files, 49 folders (1.25 linear feet)
    - Agriculture (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Asia (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - ASNE 1952-1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ASNE 1961-1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - California (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Canon 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Canon 1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Canon 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - China (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Chinard, Gilbert (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Connolly, Cyril (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Law (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Criminal Law (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Forest Genetics 1938-1949 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Forest Genetics 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Forest Genetics 1952 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Forest Genetics 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Fortune Magazine (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Freedom of Information 1954 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Freedom of Information 1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Freedom of Information 1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Freedom of Information 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Freedom of Information 1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Freedom of Information 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Freedom of Information 1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Freedom of Information 1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Freedom of Information 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Gallup Poll (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Gold Exchange (Box 4, Folder 30)